

NURUL FAREHAH BINTI RASHID

A young dedicated and pro-active person. Culturally sensitive and able to communicate with people of different backgrounds. Highly motivated, hardworking individual and have the passion in learning. A fast learner, also able to operate effectively in a team and able become a good leader whenever ask to do so.

19 OCTOBER 1992	25 YEARS OLD	FEMALE	MALAYSIAN
DATE OF BIRTH	AGE	GENDER	NATIONALITY

EDUCATION

Highest Education September 2012 - May 2017 (Finish study expected date and

convocation on November 2017)

Level: Bachelor Degree in Social Science (Politics and

Government Studies)

Institute: Universiti Malaysia Sarawak (UNIMAS)

CGPA: 2.59/ 4.00

Second Highest 2010 - 2011

Sijil Tinggi Pelajaran Malaysia (STPM)

Institute: SMK ST. Thomas, Kuching, Sarawak

CGPA: 2.75/4.00

Others 2008 - 2009

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

Institute: SMK ST. Mary, Kuching, Sarawak (Science Stream)

Results: 1A-, 3B, 1 C, 3D, 1E

2005 - 2007

Penilaian Menengah Rendah (PMR)

Institute: SMK ST. Mary, Kuching, Sarawak

Results: 3A, 4B, 1C

1999 - 2004

Ujian Penilaian Sekolah Rendah (UPSR)

Institute: SRB ST. Mary, Kuching, Sarawak

Results: 2A, 3B

PERSONALITY STRENGTH

A hardworking and well-focussed person

- ◆ A good team player and will cooperate well with the members
- Openness to learn new skills

Willingness to assist people

WORK EXPERIENCE

1) Dewan Bahasa dan Pustaka Cawangan Sarawak

Position: Intern (Administration Unit and DBP Library)

February 2017 – May 2017 (3 months)

TASK AND RESPONSIBILITY

- Sorting and recording mails
- Assisting the Telefonist
- Typing mails
- Filing
- Keeping records of daily events
- Selecting, assisting in acquiring, circulating, and maintaining library materials
- Furnishing reference, bibliographical, and readers' advisory services
- Filter and dessimination of information to users
- Assist the Librarian to digitise rare books for e-Borneo portal for online users

2) Guardian Health and Beauty Store, Kuching

Position: Cashier

August 2016-October 2016 (3 months)

TASK AND RESPONSIBILITY

- Counter service
- Assist customers to get the things they require
- Welcome customers
- Arrange and refill all the stocks
- Housekeeping like keeping the premise clean and tidy

SKILLS

Microsoft Words : Very Good

Microsoft Excel : Very Good

Power Point : Very Good

Internet Explorer : Very Good

Photography : Good

Creativity : Very Good

Languages : Can speak three (3) languages

Bahasa Melayu, English, Melanau

CONTACT

Mobile Number 014 206 2055

Email Address nfarehah921019@gmail.com

Address Lot 115 Sublot 2, Jalan Maxwell,

93000 Kuching,

Sarawak.